<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DougScore</string>
    <string name="overview_loading_data">Loading data…</string>
    <string name="details_car_daily_features">Features</string>
    <string name="details_car_daily_comfort">Comfort</string>
    <string name="details_car_daily_quality">Quality</string>
    <string name="details_car_daily_practicality">Practicality</string>
    <string name="details_car_daily_value">Value</string>
    <string name="details_car_daily_total">Total Daily</string>
    <string name="details_car_weekend_styling">Styling</string>
    <string name="details_car_weekend_acceleration">Acceleration</string>
    <string name="details_car_weekend_handling">Handling</string>
    <string name="details_car_weekend_fun_factor">Fun factor</string>
    <string name="details_car_weekend_cool_factor">Cool factor</string>
    <string name="details_car_weekend_total">Total Weekend</string>
    <string name="overview_scree_loading_data_please_wait">Loading data, please wait …</string>

    <string name="description1">There are 10 separate categories, and they’re each judged on a scale of 1 through 10 — with “1” being the worst, and “10” being the best, meaning the highest possible DougScore is 100. The ten categories are split into two separate groups: “Weekend” and “Daily.” The “Weekend” categories measure a car’s appeal to enthusiasts; in other words, how much fun it would be to drive on the weekend. The “Daily” categories, meanwhile, focus on a car’s livability and practicality.</string>
    <string name="description2">Each car is judged against all other cars and not only its segment. That’s an important point because it means these categories aren’t relative, but rather absolute: the car with the very highest DougScore is the best overall car I’ve ever driven, and the car with the lowest is the worst. The car with the highest “Weekend” score is the best enthusiast car I’ve driven; the car with the highest “Daily” score is the most practical and livable car I’ve driven.</string>
    <string name="description3">And yes, this means I’ll be comparing a Hummer H2 to a Ferrari 488; a Trabant to a Lamborghini Huracan. The H2 will probably beat the others for practicality. The 488 and Huracan will win for everything else. The Trabant will simply lose.</string>
    <string name="description4">One thing to note: since I primarily review performance cars and special cars — and since my personal opinion is that performance cars and special cars are the best cars — the DougScore is designed to be geared towards exciting cars. For instance: if a car does 0-to-60 in over 7 seconds, it gets a “1” for acceleration. That’s a reasonable time for a minivan, but I’m judging enthusiast cars — so most “normal” cars would likely end up with a low score in acceleration, and most of the other “Weekend” categories.</string>
    <string name="description5">One other note on the DougScore: I may make slight alterations, here and there, after I’ve published a car review. For instance: a car may debut with an impressive level of features and equipment, only to soon be outclassed as the car industry moves along and adds even more cool items — which could result in a lower score for that car. I also suspect I’ll give “DougScore” awards at the end of the year, and then wipe the slate clean with ever-changing definitions each year, as cars continue to get faster and more advanced.</string>
    <string name="description6">Enjoy the DougScore. Argue about the DougScore. Insist the DougScore is wrong. Use the DougScore as a metric to buy your cars. Use the DougScore as a metric to gauge my idiocy. Completely ignore the DougScore, if you want. Get tired of typing “DougScore.” But regardless of what you do, it’s here — and it’s going to give you a more complete picture of my thoughts about each car.</string>


</resources>